[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This gas is produced mainly by automobiles. It hiders the bodys ability to carry oxygen in the blood, causing serious problems for people with cardiovascular diseases.", "correct_answer": "Carbon monoxide", "incorrect_answers": ["Acid sulfates", "Carbon oxide", "Carbon dioxide"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Are tigers known to kill more humans than any other cat?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The planet Jupiter has less than 50 natural satellites.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Back to the Future, when Marty arrives in 1955, where is he?", "correct_answer": "Peabody Ranch", "incorrect_answers": ["On railroad tracks", "At George McFlys house", "At the mall"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The word physics derives from the Greek - \u03c6?\u03c3\u03b9\u03c2 (phusis), which means this.", "correct_answer": "Nature", "incorrect_answers": ["Earth", "Matter", "Force"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Ajiaco is a popular soup that originated in this Latin American country.", "correct_answer": "Colombia", "incorrect_answers": ["Argentina", "Brazil", "Venezuela"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The members of what subculture have adopted a preference for the black color?", "correct_answer": "Goth", "incorrect_answers": ["Hippie", "All of these", "Hip hop"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A tropical cyclone is classified to have reached landfall when the outer edges of the storm are over land.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Stallone has been awarded the Lifetime Achievement Award by the USA Academy of Science Fiction, Horror and Fantasy Films.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Valence is a characteristics of atoms which defines their ability to do which of the following?", "correct_answer": "Bind with other atoms", "incorrect_answers": ["Be subject to radioactive decay", "Move from one molecule to another", "Fall apart"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Why was Coca-Cola once considered an anti-Semitic company?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Coca-Cola did not have a bottling plant in Israel", "Coca-Cola was successfully doing business in the Middle East", "The manager of Coca-Colas Egyptian bottling operations announced  that Coca-Cola would never allow the Israelis a franchise"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "There are 3 types of muscle in the human body. What are they?", "correct_answer": "Cardiac, Skeletal, Smooth", "incorrect_answers": ["Voluntary, Involuntary, Nervous", "Voluntary, Involuntary, Skeletal", "Aerobic, Anaerobic, Nervous"]}]